Guide to the Artists Space Archive MSS.291
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VIII: Media
  - Subseries B: Data Storage
    - Miguel Angel Rios, "Still from Video 'A Morir (Til Death)' ", 2003 (Box 129, Disk ID: 291.3.0242)
    - Miguel Rios, "One Picture - Last One Standing", undated (Box 129, Disk ID: 291.3.0243)
    - The Mind/Body Problem: Chad Nelson, "Linda Simmons, Realtor", 2005 (Box 129, Disk ID: 291.3.0244)
    - The Mind/Body Problem: Images, January 12, 2006 (Box 129, Disk ID: 291.3.0245)
    - The Mind/Body Problem: Newer Drawings [With Contact Sheet], November 23, 2005 (Box 129, Disk ID: 291.3.0246)
    - The Mind/Body Problem: Paintings [With Contact Sheet], 2006 (Box 129, Disk ID: 291.3.0247)
    - Model Modernisms: Bove/Nicolai/Sarcevic Images, 2004 (Box 129, Disk ID: 291.3.0248)
    - [Model Modernisms]: Florian Pumhosl Hauspinakothek Images [With Correspondence], [2004] (Box 129, Disk ID: 291.3.0249)
    - Model Modernisms: [Mai-Thu Perrer], March 2005 (Box 129, Disk ID: 291.3.0250)
    - Model Modernisms: "Scans Colored Corrected", [2004] (Box 129, Disk ID: 291.3.0251)
    - Model Modernisms: "Scans Original", [2004] (Box 129, Disk ID: 291.3.0252)
    - Model Modernisms: Slides, Caption List, [2004] (Box 129, Disk ID: 291.3.0253)
    - Model Modernisms: "Slide Scans (raw)", [2005] (Box 129, Disk ID: 291.3.0254)
    - Mosten N. Halversen, "Prince (Windsor)", undated (Box 129, Disk ID: 291.3.0255)
    - Mosten N. Halversen, "The Prince (Windsor)", 2009 (Box 129, Disk ID: 291.3.0256)
    - Multitude: Ararat Images, May 23, 2002 (Box 129, Disk ID: 291.3.0257)
    - Multitude: Cari Gonzalez-Casanova, [2002] (Box 129, Disk ID: 291.3.0258)
    - Multitude: Images, September 2002 (Box 129, Disk ID: 291.3.0259)
    - Multitude: "The Tower" Images, May 23, 2002 (Box 129, Disk ID: 291.3.0260)
    - Multitude: "VH Contempo Art", September 2002 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0261)
    - nARCHITECTS, November 19, 2004 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0262)
    - nARCHITECTS: NEA Images, [March 2005] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0263)
    - nARCHITECTS: Selected Projects, March 2005 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0264)
    - Nathan Carter Images, undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0265)
    - Nina In Postition: Tom Turner, 2007 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0266)
    - Nina In Position: Tom Turner [Original Housing, Plastic Sleeve with Notation], 2007 (Box 130, Folder ID: 291.3.0266a)
    - "Nov-Dec 2003 Exhibition Images: Superstudio - Saiki - Schafer" (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0267)
    - Odile Decq: Architecte Projects Portrait, [2003] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0268)
    - Orit Raff: Documentation from the Exhibition "The Pot Calling the Kettle Black" - Burnt Pots, Gloves, undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0269)
    - Orit Raff: Documentation from the Exhibition "The Pot Calling the Kettle Black" - Installation Shots, Soaps, Polishing Cloth, undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0270)
    - Painting as Paradox: Anton Vidokle, 2002 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0271)
    - [Painting as Paradox]: Claire Corey, 2002 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0272)
    - [Painting as Paradox]: Images of Works by Claire Corey, February 11, 2002 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0273)
    - [Painting as Paradox]: Claire Corey [Correspondence], February 11, 2002 (Box 130, Folder ID: 291.3.0273a)
    - [Painting as Paradox]: Darren Wardle 2001-2002 [Copy 1] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0274)
    - [Painting as Paradox]: Darren Wardle 2001-2002 [Copy 2] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0275)
    - [Painting as Paradox]: Darren Wardle, "Urban Profane", [2002] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0276)
    - [Painting as Paradox]: Ellen Harvey, "Seeing is Believing", [2002] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0277)
    - [Painting as Paradox]: [Inaki] Gracenea "CD-1", [2002] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0278)
    - [Painting as Paradox]: [Inaki] Gracenea "CD-2", [2002] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0279)
    - [Painting as Paradox]: [Inaki] Gracenea, "Fotos 1999-2001" (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0280)
    - [Painting as Paradox]: Inaki Gracenea, "Fotos 2000-2001" (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0281)
    - [Painting as Paradox]: Jose Leon Coerrillo, "Eden, Eden", [2002] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0282)
    - [Painting as Paradox]: Matt Chansky, "Error Paintings for Lauri", [2002] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0283)
    - Painting as Paradox: Michael Phelan, "Landscape" "Floating Castle", 2002 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0284)
    - [Painting as Paradox]: Millree Hughes, "Milano", 2002 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0285)
    - Painting as Paradox: Nayda Collazo-Ilorens, "Untitled", undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0286)
    - Painting as Paradox: "Painting Book Volume 2", November 2002 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0287)
    - Painting as Paradox: Print Ad, undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0288)
    - [Painting as Paradox]: Roberto Bermejo, July 17, 2002 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0289)
    - [Painting as Paradox]: Simon Aldridge, [2002] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0290)
    - Paper Exhibition: Installation Shots, January 6, 2009 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0291)
    - Paper Exhibition: Installation Shots, January 16, 2009 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0292)
    - Parabiosis: Kendall Buster Images, 2002 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0293)
    - Patrizio di Massimo, "Documentation OAE", 2009 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0294)
    - Patrizio di Massimo, "Extract of OAE for Hypnosis", undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0295)
    - P. Bernatchez, "Chrysalide", undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0296)
    - Performa, November 20, 2005 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0297)
    - Performa "Photo Usage Specifications" Note, November 20, 2005 (Box 130, Folder ID: 291.3.0297a)
    - Performa05, November 18, 2005 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0298)
    - Performa Radio Broadcast #2 WKCR, November 11, 2005 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0299)
    - Performa Radio Broadcast #2, November 11, 2005 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0300)
    - Performa Radio #3 WKCR, November 18, 2005 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0301)
    - Performa Radio WFMU Broadcast, November 6, 2005 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0302)
    - Philip Smith Photo Works - 1970s, undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0303)
    - Project Spaces: Jordan Kantor, Mark Hamilton Installation Pictures, September 14, 2006 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0304)
    - Purloined: "Lilah's Disk", [2001] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0305)
    - Realities: United Images, undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0306)
    - REALLIFE Magazine: 25 Year Book Pictures, [2007] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0307)
    - Really: Galerie Georges-Philippe & Nathalie Vallois, Alain Bublex, Aerofiat, 1998 - 2001 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0308)
    - Recent Publications: Andrew Kuo Images, undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0309)
    - Recent Publication Slides: Hunch & Flail, Model Modernisms, Repeat Performance, [2004 - 2005] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0310)
    - Reconstructions, Assemblages: Jim Rittiman, Chris Bruce, [1991] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0311)
      Original Format: Sony MFD-2HD 3.5" Floppy Disk
    - Reign Here: Photos Andrea [Geys], November 20, 2004 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0312)
    - Repeat Performance: Robin Rhode "The Score", May 20, 2004 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0313)
    - Repeat Performance: Bradford + Rhode, June 2004 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0314)
    - Repeat Performance: Bradford + Rhode, June 2004 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0315)
    - Rip It Up and Start Again: Arthur Russell, Phill Niblock, January 18, 2010 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0316)
    - Rip It Up and Start Again: Philippe Thomas Catalogue, January 18, 2010 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0317)
    - Rip It Up and Start Again: William Burroughs Targets 1-6, January 18, 2010 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0318)
    - Robin Rhode, "Artists Space Final Cut", undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0319)
    - "RU", undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0320)
    - R.U.R: Marie Jager, "Bio + Doc", 2004 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0321)
    - Ryan Gander, [September 2005] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0322)
    - Sadar Vuga Arhitekti D.O.O., June 2002 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0323)
    - Salad Days Photos, 2004 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0324)
    - Salad Days II: Installation Images, undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0325)
    - Salad Days II: Shinya Watanabe - Kosuke Ikeda Recent Works, 2006 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0326)
    - San San Powerpoint, Spring Installation Shots, Adam Reich, 2009 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0327)
    - Sari Carez, [2005] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0328)
    - Secta, Egli [Buduroyoe], 2006 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0329)
    - Sensual Hyper Tension: Odile Decq Scans, November 12, 2004 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0330)
    - September 04 Brochure, c. 2004 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0331)
    - "Shepherd", undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0332)
    - Sign as Surface, Abstruction, Miguel Angel Rios: Press Images, September - October 2003 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0333)
    - Sign as Surface, Abstruction, Miguel Angel Rios: Press Images, September - October 2003 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0334)
    - [Sign as Surface]: Ocean D Application, May 2003 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0335)
    - Sign as Surface: Evan Douglis, Ocean D Single Track, undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0336)
    - Sign as Surface: FAT Image Files, May 2003 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0337)
    - [Sign as Surface]: Images, September 2003 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0338)
    - Sign as Surface: "Round Two Slide Scans", undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0339)
    - Sign as Surface: Symposium Pictures, September 9, 2003 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0340)
    - Simon Martin, "Wednesday Afternoon", undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0341)
    - Some Questions Concerning Technology: Les LeVeque - Word Perfect File, January 23, 1988 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0342)
      Original Format: Maxell 2S 5" Floppy Disk
    - Station to Station: Anne Kugler, 1997 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0343)
    - Station to Station: Les LeVeque, "The Free Space of the Commodity" Images, [1997] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0344)
      Original Format: Fuji Film MF 2HD 3.5" Floppy Disk
    - Superstudio: Book Scans, undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0345)
    - Superstudio: Exhibition Images, November - December 2003 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0346)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirement Note
    - Superstudio: Exhibition Images - Schafer, Saiki, November - December 2003 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0347)
    - Superstudio: Images, undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0348)
    - Superstudio: Images CD #3, undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0349)
    - Superstudio: Powerpoint Mewing/Lang, 2002 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0350)
    - Swetlana Heger: "13 TIFF Files", undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0351)
    - Swetlana Heger: Images, undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0352)
    - Swetlana Heger: "Images Revised for Print", undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0353)
    - Swetlana Heger: Original Files, undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0354)
    - [Tampering with the Reel: Installation], June 1997 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0355)
      Original Format: Dysan 5" Floppy Disk
    - Tampering with the Reel: Jalal Toufic - "Radical Closure, Artist with Bandaged Sense Organ" Installation [Copy 1], June 1997 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0356)
    - Tampering with the Reel: Jalal Toufic - "Radical Closure, Artist with Bandaged Sense Organ" Installation [Copy 2], June 1997 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0357)
    - Tampering with the Reel: Liza Johnson, [1997] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0358)
    - "Thanks", January 2007 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0359)
    - [Tigle Usx], undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0360)
    - TY Panel, January 2009 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0361)
    - Wael Shawky, "Telematch Suburb", undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0362)
    - Walid Raad, "I Only Wish That I Could Weep" (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0363)
    - When Artists Say We: Gareth & Liam, undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0364)
    - When Artists Say We: Images, March 8, 2006 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0365)
    - Uprising: ASCII File, Exdefess, [1989] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0366)
      Original Format: Fuji Film 5" Floppy Disk
    - Uprising: Exdefess, [1989] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0367)
      Capacity: 48 TPI
    - Urban Pornography, 2001 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0368)
    - [Urban Pornography], [2001] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0369)
    - [Urban Pornography], [2001] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0370)
    - [Urban Pornography], [2001] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0371)
    - Urban Pornography [Disc 1], [October 25, 2001] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0372)
    - Urban Pornography [Disc 2], [October 25, 2001] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0373)
    - Urban Pornography [Disc 3], [October 25, 2001] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0374)
    - Urban Pornography: Paul Kennedy Proposal, [2001] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0375)
    - [Untitled CD-R], undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0376)
    - [Untitled Floppy Disk], undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0397)
    - Uri Tzaig: (For Janelle), undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0377)
    - Uri Tzaig: Images for Catalogue, undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0378)
    - Uri Tzaig: Press Disc, March 2000 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0379)
    - "Video Archive", undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0380)
    - Viola Performance, March 20, 2007 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0381)
    - Whirlwind: Laurie Anderson - Bids & Invoices, [1998] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0382)
    - Word Perfect Working Copy, [1989] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0383)
    - Wunderkammer: Karin Fong, [May 2002] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0384)
    - Wunderkammer: Olive PR, [2002] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0385)
    - [Zaha Hadid], [June 2003] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0386)
    - Zaha Hadid: Car Park and Terminus Hoenheim-Nord Strasbourg Press, [2003] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0387)
    - Zaha Hadid: Centro Per Le Arti Contemporanee, undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0388)
    - Zaha Hadid: Contemporary Arts Center Images, [2003] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0389)
    - Zaha Hadid: Images [Cin and Prile Tower], [2003] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0390)
    - Zaha Hadid: Images, Press Release, Project List, undated (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0391)
    - Zaha Hadid: Installation Shots, [2003] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0392)
    - Zaha Hadid: PTAC_CAC PAL, June 2003 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0393)
    - Zaha Hadid: PTAC_CAC PAL, June 2003 (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0394)
    - Zaha Hadid: Shipping Images, [2003] (Box 130, Disk ID: 291.3.0395)
- OVERSIZE Series I: Exhibition Files
  - Artists As Filmmakers Series: Poster, March 22, 1975 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - "2 Performances" Simone Forti, Peter Van Riper: Posters, November 14, 1975 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Beth Anderson with Paul Cotton: Ear Magazine [2 of 2], November 20, 1976 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Artists Super 8 Film Exposition: Schedule II, Vertical Projection Note, May 11, 1977 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Audio Works: Gallery Maps, Research, January 21, 1978 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Architectural Manifestos: Bernard Tschumi Reproduction Proofs [2 of 2], April 3, 1978 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Eric Bogosian "The Garden" Performance: Poster [2 of 2], November 2, 1978 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Pieter Holstein "The Waterfall": Brochure [2 of 2], January 6, 1979 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Ten Artists: Poster, September 9, 1979 (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - 7 Toronto Artists: Artists' Materials, Correspondence [2 of 2], April 5, 1980 (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - Reese Williams: Poster, May 17, 1980 (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Film at Artists Space: Poster, November 14, [1980] (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Joel Hubaut: "Une Idee En L'air" Brochure [3 of 3], November 30, 1980 (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - Glenys Johnson "Wall Drawing": Correspondence, October 24, 1981 (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - "Men Who Are Men" by Jeff Balsmeyer: Poster, February 7, [1982] (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - A Likely Story: Ronald Jones "Theories of Art Criticism" Poster, February 20, 1982 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - Evening Series of Readings and Films: Posters of Related Events, April 1, 1982 (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - Young Fluxus: Research Materials, April 10, 1982 (Box 122, Folder 12)
  - Installations by Barbara Noah, Ken Lim, Redd Ekks: Exhibition Notes, November 6, 1982 (Box 122, Folder 13)
  - Dorit Cypis "Shadow to Frame": Poster, 1983 (Box 122, Folder 14)
  - Installation: Kevin Labadie Drawing, April 9, 1983 (Folder 13)
  - Los Angeles/New York Exchange: Victor Henderson Poster, New York Research, May 21, 1983 (Box 122, Folder 15)
  - Artists Space Benefit, "100s of Drawings" Reception: Contact Sheets, 1984 (Box 122, Folder 16)
  - "Layout for Show at Artists Space" by Dara Birnbaum, 1984 (Box 122, Folder 17)
  - Three Individual Installations: Posters, April 7, 1984 (Box 122, Folder 18)
  - A Decade of New Art: Publication Text Proofs [2 of 2], May 31, 1984 (Box 122, Folder 19)
  - U.S. Projects - Jerry Beck: Budget Notes, Exhibition Installation Instructions [2 of 2], May 25, 1985 (Box 122, Folder 20)
  - U.S. Projects: Patricia Thornley Installation Map, May 25, 1985 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Selections From the Artists File: Publication Text Draft, September 21, 1985 (Box 122, Folder 21)
  - Moderns in Mind: Gerome Kamrowski Clippings, April 12, 1986 (Box 122, Folder 22)
  - Moderns In Mind: Gordon Guslow "Man Is Space" Poster, April 12, 1986 (Folder 12)
  - The Fairy Tale: Curt Belshe, Lise Prown Installation Plans, October 30, 1986 (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - The Fairy Tale: Posters, October 30, 1986 (Box 122, Folder 23)
  - Mike Kelly - Plato's Cave, Rothko's Chapel, Lincoln's Profile: Publication Layout Draft, December 5, 1986 (Box 122, Folder 24)
  - TV Sandino: 25th Ann Arbor Film Festival Poster, March 10, 1987 (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - Architecture and Design Project Series: Ian and Lynn Bader Proposal Maps, May 21, 1987 (Box 122, Folder 25)
  - Calvert Coggeshall and Frederick Hammersley: Gallery Map, May 21, 1987 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Tourist Attractions - Readings Organized by Ann Turyn and Brian Wallis: Posters, June 25, 1987 (Box 122, Folder 26)
  - We the People: Research Materials, November 21, 1987 (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - Social Spaces: Stephen Glassman Sculpture Poster, January 14, 1988 (Box 126, Folder 10)
  - The London Project: Installation Map, Publication Essay Draft, April 1, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 27)
  - Min Joong Art: Posters, September 29, 1988 (Box 126, Folder 11)
  - The AIDS Crisis is Not Over: Poster, Publication Proof, November 17, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 28)
  - In the Streets - Protest Films From the 60s and 80s: Poster, January 8, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 29)
  - Coming Soon - Works In Progress by Five Filmmakers: Posters, May 19, 1989 (Box 122, Folder 30)
  - Project - Don Stinson, Perspective the State of Existing in Space Before the Eye: Gallery Maps, September 28, 1989 (Box 126, Folder 12)
  - Body Language: The Film Society of Lincoln Center and MOMA Department of Film - New Directors, New Films Poster, March 16, 1990 (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Erawa-Era Was: Paquin/Stoddard "Castaway Hills" Preliminary Drawings (Photocopies), April 19, 1990 (Box 122, Folder 31)
  - Uprising - Videotapes on the Palestinian Resistance: Poster, Press Clipping, November 16, 1989 (Box 122, Folder 32)
  - Coming Attractions - New Narratives on Race and Sexuality: Poster, May 25, 1990 (Box 122, Folder 33)
  - Recycling LA: [Cedar Sinai Street Scene Photocopy], May 31, 1990 (Box 126, Folder 13)
  - Recycling LA: Research, May 31, 1990 (Box 122, Folder 34)
  - Teaching TV: Posters, November 9, 1990 (Box 122, Folder 35)
  - Reframing the Family: Poster, January 17, 1991 (Box 126, Folder 14)
  - Reframing the Family: Press Clippings, January 17, 1991 (Box 122, Folder 36)
  - Putt-Modernism: Brochure Drafts, August 1, 1992 (Folder 6 Right)
  - Putt-Modernism: Exhibition Development [2 of 2], August 1, 1992 (Box 122, Folder 37)
  - Ping Chong: Exhibition Brochure Draft, Final Published Version, October 17, 1992 (Box 126, Folder 15)
  - Robert Farber - I Thought I Had Time: Gallery Maps, October 17, 1992 (Box 122, Folder 38)
  - VISUAL AIDS: Gallery Floorplan (Photocopies), December 1, 1992 (Box 122, Folder 39)
  - Divine Comedies - John deFazio: Publication Layout Draft, December 12, 1992 (Box 122, Folder 40)
  - Sighting the Gallery - Joel Sanders, Scott Shark: Project Maps, December 12, 1992 (Box 122, Folder 41)
  - A New World Order III - Godzilla: Performance Research, Maps, February 18, 1993 (Box 122, Folder 42)
  - Blankets - Suzie Brandt: Gallery Map, February 18, 1993 (Box 122, Folder 43)
  - Rage and Desire Poster, [March 16, 1993] (Box 122, Folder 44)
  - Activated Walls: Announcement Postcard, Gallery Maps, April 13, 1993 (Box 122, Folder 45)
  - Artists Space Multiples: John Giorno "Treat a Complete Stranger," "The World is Getting" Drafts, May 29, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Carmen Herrera: STET, Noticias de Arte Newspapers, June 3, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Putt-Modernism: Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art Poster, August 7, 1993 (Box 126, Folder 16)
  - Artists Select I - Celia Alvarez Munoz, Diana Rodriguez Gil Gallery Map, November 20, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - What's a Mother To Do? Angela Fremont: The Dance Theater Workshop Newsletter, Gallery Map, January 3, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - AIDS Forum - Carl Tandatnick: Preliminary Mock-Up, January 25, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - AIDS Forum - Glen Sacks: "Miracle House" Image, March 29, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Selections From The Artists File: Todd Slaughter Gallery Maps [2 of 2], September 10, 1994 (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - Six Moons Over Oaxaca: Food Posters, October 29, 1994 (Box 126, Folder 17)
  - Las Americas - The Return of Martin Steel: Osualdo Romberg Images [2 of 2], January 28, 1995 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Sit Down and Watch It, Authors In Search of a Publisher: Posters, April 18, 1995 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Customized Terror: Exhibition Brochure Draft, May 20, 1995 (Box 126, Folder 18)
  - Anne Marie Jugnet: Hedendaagse Franse Kunst In Nederland Newspaper, November 11, 1995 (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - Vincent Beaurin: "Stills From Videotape 'Vanitas in a Bathroom' ", November 21, 1995 (Folder 7)
  - Squat Cafe: X/Y Centre Georges Pompidou Poster, April 3, 1996 (Box 126, Folder 19)
  - "Gravity and Grace" by Chris Kraus: Poster, June 13, [1996] (Box 126, Folder 20)
  - A Strategy Hinted At - New Conceptual Artists: Bruce Nauman MOMA Newspaper, Constructions Images Michael Klein Gallery Brochure, September 6, 1996 (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - Station to Station: Kristin Lucas Drawings, "Know Where to Hide" Postcard, April 12, 1997 (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - Present Tense - The Architecture of George Ranalli: Press Clippings, November 17, 1997 (Box 123, Folder 13)
  - Digital Mapping: Architecture as Media: Newsline Online Newsletter, March 28, 1998 (Box 123, Folder 14)
  - 'Nearly the Solstice' Party Poster, June 26, 1998 (Box 123, Folder 15)
  - Whirlwind: "Laurie Anderson Scribbles", September 19, 1998 (Box 123, Folder 16)
  - Society for Collective Investigation: Matthew Bakkom Posters, December 16, 1999 (Box 126, Folder 21)
  - Architeture Research Office: Leslie Gill Images, February 3, 2000 (Box 123, Folder 17)
  - Anywhere But Here: Airline Graphs, Jetlag Images, June 1, 2000 (Box 123, Folder 18)
  - Uri Tzaig - Duel: Poster Inserts Drafts, September 9, 2000 (Box 123, Folder 19)
  - Really: 3 Marked Decks by Janice Kerbel Poster, January 27, 2001 (Box 123, Folder 20)
  - "Pictures" At An Exhibition: Gallery Images, May 24, 2001 (Box 123, Folder 21)
  - Urban Pornography: Exhibition Brochure Draft, October 25, 2001 (Box 123, Folder 22)
  - Context and Conceptualism: Exhibition Brochure Draft, Press Clipping, January 12, 2002 (Box 123, Folder 23)
  - Context and Conceptualism: Siemon Allen Posters, January 12, 2002 (Box 126, Folder 22)
  - Point of View, Dog-Cam Project: Nobuhira Narumi Posters, January 12, 2002 (Box 126, Folder 23)
  - Documents: Touhami Ennadre Catalogue Draft, September 5, 2002 (Box 123, Folder 24)
  - Multitude: Corine Borgnet Images, September 5, 2002 (Box 123, Folder 25)
  - Painting as Paradox: Exhibition Brochure Draft, November 7, 2002 (Box 123, Folder 26)